<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ETL/ELT on Lior Kaufman</title>
    <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/tags/etl/elt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ETL/ELT on Lior Kaufman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/tags/etl/elt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DBT Source automation</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/dbt-source-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/dbt-source-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Streamline Your Data Onboarding with DBT Codegen package Introduction
In today’s data-driven world, dbt (data build tool) has become the go-to open-source transformation tool for turning raw data into actionable insights. In this post, we’ll explore dbt’s organized layer approach (staging, intermediate, and marts/final tables) and how automation can make onboarding new sources more efficient, using a real-life example from my own experience.
DBT: Data Transformation Done Right
DBT allows data engineers and analysts to perform complex data manipulations using a simple, maintainable, and version-controlled codebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Run Jobs</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/cloudrun-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blogs/cloudrun-jobs/</guid>
      <description>Checking Out Google Cloud Run Jobs With a Practical Example Deploy a Dockerized Python script to Google Cloud Platform using Cloud Run Jobs. In this article we will write a simple python data extraction script, deploy it to Google Cloud Run Jobs container and discuss the status of cloud run jobs — google newest container as a service offering.
Prerequisites to follow this guide:
Local installation of Docker Google Cloud CLI tool Google Cloud account with billing enabled Official overview of Cloud Run Jobs from Google Although Cloud Run services are a good fit for containers that run indefinitely listening for HTTP requests, Cloud Run jobs may be a better fit for containers that run to completion and don’t serve requests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
